Guide to the Clark, Hall, and Peck and White Brothers Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- White Brothers, 1880s-1982; Series I
  - Other Connecticut cities and towns
    - West Haven
      - Abstracts of title
        - Malden Street, Maltby Avenue, Maple Street, Maple Road (First Avenue), Marion Street, Marsh Street, Marshall Street (Brown Street), Marks Drive, Martin Street, Meadowbrook Road, Marydale Road, Martin Lane (Box 861)
        - Main Street (North and south, street addresses 1 through 449) (Box 862)
        - Main Street (North and south, street addresses 450 to end, non-street number files) (Box 863)
        - Medford Street, Meloy Road, "Merrill Estate" (Cynthia M., Forest Road), Miami Street, Michael Drive, Middle Street, Middlefield Road, Milhaven Drive, Mill Street, Mills Drive, Miner Road, "Minor Park" (Flat system), Malcom Road (Box 864)
        - N. and S. Milford Tpke. (Orange Avenue, street addresses to 600) (Box 865)
        - N. and S. Milford Tpke. (Orange Avenue, street addresses from 601 to end, non-street number files), Milford Avenue Developments: "Alling Heights," "Blythdale," "City View Terrace," "City View Terrace Annex," "Hoffman Park," "Hoffman Park Annex," "Home Gardens," "Orange Avenue Gardens," "West Haven Gardens" (Box 866)
        - Milton Avenue, Milton Court, Mix Avenue (First Avenue), Mohawk Drive, Monahan Place, Monteith Street, Morgan Lane, Morgan Street (Beach Street) (Box 867)
        - Morris Avenue (Derby Avenue), Morris Street (Aims Point), Morrissey Lane, Morse Avenue, Mountain View Street, Mount Pleasant Road, Mullen Road, Myra Road, Myrtle Avenue, Nacca Road, Nashawena Avenue, New Street, Newbern Street (Box 868)
        - Noble Street, Nonquit Street, Norfolk Street (Box 869)
        - North Place, North Street, Northrop Road, North Union Avenue (Union Avenue), Norwell Street, Oak Road, Oak Street, Ocala Street, "Offield Park," Ogden Street, Oleander Avenue, Oliver Lane, "Orange Park" (Box 870)
          For Orange Avenue, see Milford Tpke.
        - Ocean Avenue (Street addresses 1 through 599) (Box 871)
        - Ocean Avenue (Street addresses 600 through 1261, non-street number files) (Box 872)
        - Ocean Avenue Developments: Bradley Park, "Colonial Park," Peter Aims Farm, "Prospect Beach," Prospect Terrace," "Sea Bluff," Orange Terrace (Box 873)
          For "Woodycrest", see 381-389 Ocean Avenue.
        - Orchard Street, Orford Road, Orford Street, "Oriental Park" (Peck Avenue), Orion Street, Orlando Street, Ormond Street, Orne Street, Orton Street, Osborne Avenue, Overlook Avenue, Ownly Avenue, Oxbow Lane, Painter Avenue, "Paradise Gardens" (Box 874)
        - Park Avenue, Park Street, Parker Avenue, Parkridge Road, Park Terrace Avenue, Park View Terrace (Box 875)
        - Paul Avenue, Pauline Avenue, Peabody Street, Peck Avenue, Peck Lane, Peck Street (Box 876)
        - Penn Street (Union Avenue), Peter Lane, Pheasant Road, Phillips Terrace, Phipps Drive, Pine Street (Wellwood Manor), Plainfield Avenue, Platt Avenue, Prindle Road, Priscilla Road (Box 877)
        - Prospect Avenue, Prospect Place, Prospect Street, Prudden Street, Putney Drive, Railroad Avenue, "Ranchwood," Ranchwood Drive, Randolph Street, Rangeley Street, Raymond Street, Ricardo Street ("Home View Terrace") (Box 878)
        - Richards Place, Richards Street (Box 879)
        - Richmond Avenue, "Richmond Avenue Development," Ridge Road, Robart Street, Robert Street, Robin Road, Rochdale Terrace, Rock Street (Beach), Rockdale Road (Box 880)
        - Rockview Street, Rockefeller Avenue, Rockledge Street, Rodney Street, Roosevelt Avenue (Sound View Heights), Ruby Road, Ruden Lane, Ruden Place, Ruden Street, Roy Street, Sanford Street, Sarah Court (Box 881)
        - Savin Avenue (Odd number street addresses 299 through 813-815), "Graham Manor," "Lots at Graham Manor" (Box 882)
        - Savin Avenue (Even number street addresses), "Savin Avenue Condominiums" (Savin Park) (Box 883)
        - Sawmill Road, Schroder & Anderson, Scott Street, Seaview Avenue, "Seaview Terrace," Sunset Road, Templeton Street (Box 884)
        - Schoolhouse Lane, Second Avenue Terrace, Shady Lane, Sharon Avenue, Sharon Street, Shingle Hill Road (Main Street), Shumway Street (W. Spring Street), Simon Place, Sky Line Drive, Smith Street (Box 885)
        - Second Avenue (Odd number street addresses 85 through 725, non-street number files) (Box 886)
        - Second Avenue (Even number street addresses 40 through 726, non-street number files) (Box 887)
        - Sorensen Road, "Sound View Heights," "Sound View Heights & Annex #1 & #2," South Street, Spring Street (Box 888)
        - Spruce Street (Offield Park and Wellwood Manor), Staehly Road, Stevens Avenue, "Stevens Heights" (York Street), Strathmore Road, Suman Street, Summer Street, Sundance Circle, Sunflower Circle, Susquehanna Avenue, Swampscott Street (Box 889)
        - Sugar Bush Circle, Sycaway Street, Taft Avenue, Thomas Street (Box 890)
        - Third Avenue, Third Avenue Ext. (Box 891)
        - Thompson Street, Tower Road, Treadwell Street, Trescott Street, Terrace Avenue, Terrace Avenue Ext., Tetlow Street, "Thill Park" (Front Avenue), Thill Street (Box 892)
        - Tile Street, Trumbull Street, Tuthill Street, Twin Circle Road, Tyler Avenue, Usher Court, Vernon Street, View Street, Voss Road, Wade Street, Wallace Street (Box 893)
        - Union Avenue, North Union Avenue (Box 894)
        - Valley Brook Road, Waban Street, Ward Street, Wharton Street, Wales Street (Box 895)
        - Walnut Street, Ward Place, Warner Avenue, Water Street, Wenham Street, Westfield Street (Box 896)
        - Washington Avenue (West side, even number street addresses 36 through 832) (Box 897)
        - Washington Avenue (East side, odd number street addresses 17 through 851) (Box 898)
        - "Washington Manor," Washington Manor Avenue, Wenham Street, West Prospect Street, West Spring Street (Box 899)
        - "Wellwood Manor," "West Haven Gardens" (Milford Tpke.), "West Haven Heights," "West Haven Park" (Highland Street), West Main Street, "West Main Street Terrace" (Savin Avenue), "Weston" (945-947 Campbell Avenue), White Street (Brown Street), Whitney Lane, Wildwood Terrace, West Walk (Savin Rock Condominiums) (Box 900)
        - William Street, Willow Street, Wilson Avenue, Windsock Road, Winfred Street, (Derby Avenue), Wingtip Road (Box 901)
        - Winslow Drive, Wood Street, Woodbridge Road, Woodfield Road, Woodhill Lane, Woodland Street, Woodlawn Street, Woodmont Road, Woodruff Street, Woodside Path, Woodvale Road, Woody Lane, Yates Street (Box 902)
          For Woody Crest, see Osborne Avenue.
        - York Street, Zegmont Street (Box 903)
        - Miscellaneous West Haven files (Box 904)
      - Flat files
        - Aimes Farm (Box 905)
        - Roger Allen Land (Box 905)
        - Alling Park (Box 905)
        - Alling's Crossing Road (Box 905)
        - Allingtown Elementary School site (Box 905)
        - Baybrook Shopping Center Inc. (Box 905)
        - Benham Hill Homes (Box 905)
        - "Birchwood Gardens" (Box 905)
        - "Birchwood Gardens & Glen Oak" (Box 906)
        - Brown, William B. (N. Blohm Street 58-71) (Box 906)
        - City View Terrace (Box 906)
        - Colonial Park (Box 906)
        - "Country Hills" (Sections 1-5) (Box 906)
        - Dinardo Realty Co. (Box 906)
        - 218-224 Elm Street (Box 906)
        - "Elm Terrace" (Box 907)
        - "Falls View Heights" (Box 907)
        - Fillipelli, John (Box 907)
        - "Forest Ridge" (Box 907)
        - Forest Theatre (Box 907)
        - Funk, Harold and Elizabeth (Box 907)
        - Gill, Sarah M. L. (Grantor-grantee) (Box 907)
        - Hall Street (South side -Land for School purposes) (Box 908)
        - "Harbor View" (Box 908)
        - "Hilton Manor" (Box 908)
        - "Hoggan Land" (Box 908)
        - "Kelsey Heights" (Box 908)
        - Kelsey, George R. (Box 908)
        - 88 Knox Street (Box 908)
        - Landkowski, Alex and Caroline (Prindle Road) (Box 908)
        - Logiodices, Pasquale (Estate) (Box 908)
        - "Meadowbrook" (Section 3) (Box 908)
        - Miles Laboratories (Box 909)
        - "Millhaven Heights" (Box 909)
        - Millhaven Heights (Section 4) (Box 909)
        - 345 Morgan Lane (Box 909)
        - Morgan Lane (Annie Russell Miles estate) (Box 909)
        - Morris, Henry (Land of, west part of town located near Usher's Sea Bluff) (Box 909)
        - Morrissey Land Development (Box 909)
        - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (Box 909)
        - Nordman, Magdalene (Grantor-grantee) (Box 909)
        - Oak Grove (Box 909)
        - 1020 Ocean Avenue (Box 909)
        - Ocean View Condominiums (Box 910)
        - Offield Park (Box 910)
        - 855-899 Orange Avenue (Box 910)
        - "Orange Park" (Box 910)
        - Paradise Gardens, Paradise Gardens Annex (Box 910)
        - Pegnataro Realty Co. (Box 910)
        - Peter Aimes Farm (Box 911)
        - "Phillips Manor" (Box 911)
        - Printer Avenue (Rear of high school site) (Box 911)
        - "Printer Park" (Box 911)
        - "Ranchwood" (Box 911)
        - Richmond Avenue Development (Box 911)
        - Rivoli Theatre (Box 911)
        - 460 Savin Avenue (Box 911)
        - Savin Rock Urban Renewal Area 2 "Parcel H" (Box 911)
        - "Sea Terrace" (Box 912)
        - Second Avenue (Box 912)
        - "Shingle Hill" (Sections 1-2) (Box 912)
        - "Shore Haven" (Box 912)
        - "Sound View Heights" (Box 912)
        - Spangenberg, John and Ann (30 Daggett Street) (Box 912)
        - Emil Staely land (Box 912)
        - Strathmore Homes (Box 912)
        - "Sundance Circle", 2 (Box 913)
        - Voss Industrial Center (Box 913)
        - Voss Property (Construction company) (Box 913)
        - 7-39 Wales Street (Box 913)
        - "Wellwood Manor" (Box 913)
        - Weiderman Brothers Brewery (Box 913)
        - West Haven Heights (Box 913)
        - West Haven Homes (Box 913)
        - West Haven Industrial Park (Box 914)
        - "West Haven Manor" (Box 914)
        - West Shore Terrace (Box 914)
        - Woodvale Subdivision (Box 914)
    - Westbrook
      - Abstracts of title (Box 915)
      - Flat files (Box 915)
    - Westport
      - Abstracts of title (Box 916)
      - Flat file (Box 916)
    - Wolcott abstract of title (Box 916)
    - Woodbridge
      - Index card locator file (A-L) (Box 917)
      - Index card locator file (M-Z) (Box 918)
      - Abstracts of title
        - 1-60 (Box 919)
        - 61-120 (Box 920)
        - 121-180 (Box 921)
        - 181-240 (Box 922)
        - 241-315 (Box 923)
        - 316-380 (Box 924)
        - 381-460 (Box 925)
        - 461-520 (Box 926)
        - 521-580 (Box 927)
        - 581-660 (Box 928)
        - 661-719 (Box 929)
        - 720-797 (Box 930)
      - Flat files
        - 71, 87, 132, 143, 144, 145, 146, 147, 148 (Box 931)
        - 149, 203, 238, 240, 277, 360, 395, 403, 418, 430, 445, 446, 447, 455 (Box 932)
        - 462, 496, 497, 547, 551, 593, 609, 612, 615, 638, 640, 641, 642 (Box 933)
        - 656, 690, 693, 698, 702, 704, 720, 788 (Box 934)
  - Grantor-grantee files (All cities and towns)
    - Index A-Z (Box 935)
    - A-B (Box 935)
    - B (continued) (Box 936)
    - C-E (Box 937)
    - F-G (Box 938)
    - H (Box 939)
    - I-L (Box 940)
    - M-O (Box 941)
    - P-R (Box 942)
    - S-V (Box 943)
    - W-Z (Box 944)
  - Unidentified flat files (Box 945)
  - Probate Records (Box 946)
- Clark, Hall and Peck, 1890s-1982; Series II
  This series contains documentation of title searches performed by Clark, Hall, and Peck, primarily between the 1890s and 1982. Since Clark, Hall, and Peck was, along with White Brothers, one of the leading real estate law firms, there are records relating to most, though not all, substantial projects and developers in the New Haven County area.
  The original arrangement of the Clark, Hall, and Peck records has been retained. Although this series follows a geographic district arrangement similar to the White Brothers series, the two firms had different methods of accessing their files. Like the White Brothers series, the entries related to New Haven and its associated areas (Annex, Westville, and an additional area known as District A) appear first, followed by other Connecticut cities and towns. Within the arrangement for each city or town, abstracts of title are found in order of size of the documentation, i.e. folded or flat files. The amount of materials assembled for each tract determined whether they are located in folded bundles (small) or flat files (medium). Unlike the White Brothers series, there are no project files. Although the largest number of properties will be represented among the folded bundles, the researcher should also examine the entries under the flat file heading to ensure that all materials are located.
  Materials are arranged by a geographic district system similar to the White Brothers series. New Haven is organized into a system of forty-three districts (1-43), but there are no records for district 34. In addition, there are three other areas associated with New Haven: the Annex (the area east of New Haven Harbor and the Quinnipiac River) is District 50, Westville (the area to the northwest of New Haven) is District 70, and District A (area near the New Haven-Hamden town lines). The records from New Haven's Westville section follow those from the Annex (beginning with box 1184), while abstracts of title from District A appear after the Westville records (beginning with box 1253A). Other Connecticut cities and towns are arranged alphabetically beginning with box 1323.
  For New Haven and some of the other cities and towns, there are alphabetical index card locator files for the streets. In the box listing, the researcher should locate the appropriate town and then find the index card locator file box containing the cards for the desired street. When consulting the index card box, the researcher will find that the cards are filed alphabetically by street name. If there is a card for a particular property, the researcher will find a code in one of the upper corners. The number includes the district designation along with a number assigned by the law firm to that particular property. Examples of the numeration are 3-259, Annex 2-653, Annex 47, or Westville 2943. Once the code is found, the researcher would refer back to the box listing (under the abstracts of title heading) to find which box contains the materials associated with the particular code number.
  In addition to the folded abstracts, the researcher should also review the listings for flat files (numerical and alphabetical), owner name files, and miscellaneous files for the specific town so all materials from this series may be located. Flat files (numerical and alphabetical) for New Haven and its associated areas are arranged beginning with box 1254. At the end of the New Haven alphabetical flat files, there is a unique alphabetical index card file indicating records of actions taken by the Board of Aldeman and City Engineering Department by street name (box 1321).
  Records from other Connecticut cities and towns, arranged alphabetically, appear after the end of the New Haven and associated areas records. Available materials vary by town, but can include an atlas or map book, index card locator files (street and owner), folded abstracts, and flat files. The procedure for accessing these files depends upon the particular aids available for a specific town but is similar to locating New Haven properties.
  The researcher should be aware that some Town of Orange records were commingled with West Haven's District 14 records. West Haven is the only municipality, other than New Haven, in which the abstracts are organized by a district system (Districts 1-14). After 1964, Clark, Hall, and Peck began to consistently use the designation Orange for all records from that town and the term West Haven for all abstracts from West Haven's numerical districts. The West Haven records are arranged as follows: abstracts from West Haven numerical districts 1-14, flat files from the numerical districts, West Haven flat files, and flat files from Orange when those records were included in West Haven's District 14.
  Another index card locator file (box 2134) containing an alphabetical listing of all the names of property owners (individuals and businesses) for whom Clark, Hall and Peck performed title searches is found after the records for other Connecticut cities and towns. Each index card lists the numbers of all abstracts which correspond to that person's or firm's name.
  Probate records are located at the end of the Clark, Hall and Peck series. An alphabetical index card file of last names is followed by the probate file extracts, also arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - New Haven
    - Index card locator files
      - Streets
        - Academy Street - Avon Street (Box 947)
        - Bailey Street - Bradley Place (Box 948)
        - Brewery Street - Chambers Street (Box 949)
        - Chapel Street - Colorado Street (Box 950)
        - Columbus Avenue - Davis Street (Box 951)
        - Day Street - East Pearl Street (Box 952)
        - East Rock Road - English Street (Box 953)
        - Essex Street - Fort Hale Road (Box 954)
        - Foster Street - Glen Haven Road (Box 955)
        - Glen View Terrace - Hamilton Street (Box 956)
        - Hard Street - Howard Avenue (Box 957)
        - Howard Street - Kilday Lane (Box 958)
        - Kimberly Avenue - Lighthouse Road (Box 959)
        - Lighthouse Point Road - Massachusetts Avenue (Box 960)
        - Maureen Street - New Street (Box 961)
        - Newhall Street - Orchard Street (Box 962)
        - Osborn Avenue - Prince Street (Box 963)
        - Prindle Street - Roma Street (Box 964)
        - Roosevelt Street - Sherland Avenue (Box 965)
        - Sherman Avenue - Stratford Avenue (Box 966)
        - Strong Street - Valley Place So. (Box 967)
        - Valley Street - West Elm Street (Box 968)
        - Westerleigh Road - Willow Court (Box 969)
        - Willow Street - Young Street (Box 970)
    - Folded abstracts of title
      - 1-1 - 1-95 (Box 971)
      - 1-96 - 1-180 (Box 972)
      - 1-181 - 1-280 (Box 973)
      - 1-281 - 1-341, 2-1 - 2-30 (Box 974)
      - 2-31 - 2-110 (Box 975)
      - 2-111 - 2-199 (Box 976)
      - 2-200 - 2-299 (Box 977)
      - 2-300 - 2-410 (Box 978)
      - 2-411 - 2-495 (Box 979)
      - 2-496 - 2-599 (Box 980)
      - 2-600 - 2-685 (Box 981)
      - 3-1 - 3-75 (Box 982)
      - 3-76 - 3-134 (Box 983)
      - 3-135 - 3-185 (Box 984)
      - 3-186 - 3-245 (Box 985)
      - 3-246 - 3-312 (Box 986)
      - 4-1 - 4-69 (Box 987)
      - 4-71 - 4-139 (Box 988)
      - 4-140 - 4-190 (Box 989)
      - 4-191 - 4-239 (Box 990)
      - 4-240 - 4-339 (Box 991)
      - 4-340 - 4-405 (Box 992)
      - 4-406 - 4-453 (Box 993)
      - 5-1 - 5-49 (Box 994)
      - 5-50 - 5-115 (Box 995)
      - 5-116 - 5-179 (Box 996)
      - 5-180 - 5-244 (Box 997)
      - 5-245 - 5-310 (Box 998)
      - 5-311 - 5-383 (Box 999)
      - 6-1 - 6-55 (Box 1000)
      - 6-56 - 6-134 (Box 1001)
      - 6-135 - 6-209 (Box 1002)
      - 6-210 - 6-290 (Box 1003)
      - 6-291 - 6-389 (Box 1004)
      - 6-390 - 6-489 (Box 1005)
      - 6-490 - 6-569 (Box 1006)
      - 6-570 - 6-610, 7-1 - 7-30 (Box 1007)
      - 7-31 - 7-129 (Box 1008)
      - 7-130 - 7-202 (Box 1009)
      - 7-203 - 7-271 (Box 1010)
      - 7-272 - 7-359 (Box 1011)
      - 7-360 - 7-440 (Box 1012)
      - 7-441 - 7-514 (Box 1013)
      - 7-515 - 7-535, 8-1 -8-55 (Box 1014)
      - 8-56 - 8-120 (Box 1015)
      - 8-121 - 8-199 (Box 1016)
      - 8-200 - 8-275 (Box 1017)
      - 8-276 - 8-355 (Box 1018)
      - 8-356 - 8-454 (Box 1019)
      - 8-455 - 8-526, 9-1 -9-19 (Box 1020)
      - 9-20 - 9-90 (Box 1021)
      - 9-91 - 9-179 (Box 1022)
      - 9-180 - 9-274 (Box 1023)
      - 9-275 - 9-349 (Box 1024)
      - 9-350 - 9-421, 10-1 - 10-15 (Box 1025)
      - 10-16 - 10-99 (Box 1026)
      - 10-100 - 10-142, 11-1 - 11-29 (Box 1027)
      - 11-30 - 11-109 (Box 1028)
      - 11-110 - 11-200 (Box 1029)
      - 11-201 - 11-299 (Box 1030)
      - 11-300 - 11-402 (Box 1031)
      - 11-403 - 11-421, 12-1 - 12-89 (Box 1032)
      - 12-90 - 12-174 (Box 1033)
      - 12-175 - 12-245 (Box 1034)
      - 12-246 - 12-349 (Box 1035)
      - 12-350 - 12-430 (Box 1036)
      - 12-431 - 12-480 (Box 1037)
      - 12-481 - 12-527, 13-1 - 13-14 (Box 1038)
      - 13-15 - 13-80 (Box 1039)
      - 13-81 - 13-160 (Box 1040)
      - 13-161 - 13-249 (Box 1041)
      - 13-250 - 13-329 (Box 1042)
      - 13-330 - 13-387, 14-1 - 14-19 (Box 1043)
      - 14-20 - 14-84 (Box 1044)
      - 14-85 - 14-174 (Box 1045)
      - 14-175 - 14-254 (Box 1046)
      - 14-255 - 14-360 (Box 1047)
      - 14-361 - 14-434 (Box 1048)
      - 14-435 - 14-482, 15-1 - 15-29 (Box 1049)
      - 15-30 - 15-119 (Box 1050)
      - 15-120 - 15-220 (Box 1051)
      - 15-221 - 15-333 (Box 1052)
      - 16-1 - 16-55 (Box 1053)
      - 16-56 - 16-120 (Box 1054)
      - 16-121 - 16-179 (Box 1055)
      - 16-180 - 16-240 (Box 1056)
      - 16-241 - 16-299 (Box 1057)
      - 16-300 - 16-360 (Box 1058)
      - 16-361 - 16-420 (Box 1059)
      - 16-421 - 16-494 (Box 1060)
      - 16-495 - 16-549 (Box 1061)
      - 16-550 - 16-559, 17-1 - 17-50 (Box 1062)
      - 17-51 - 17-110 (Box 1063)
      - 17-111 - 17-210 (Box 1064)
      - 17-211 - 17-290 (Box 1065)
      - 17-291 - 17-365 (Box 1066)
      - 17-366 - 17-427 (Box 1067)
      - 17-428 - 17-485 (Box 1068)
      - 17-486 - 17-564 (Box 1069)
      - 18-1 - 18-80 (Box 1070)
      - 18-81 - 18-150 (Box 1071)
      - 18-151 - 18-219 (Box 1072)
      - 18-220 - 18-270 (Box 1073)
      - 18-271 - 18-359 (Box 1074)
      - 18-360 - 18-424 (Box 1075)
      - 18-425 - 18-499 (Box 1076)
      - 18-500 - 18-575 (Box 1077)
      - 18-576 - 18-645 (Box 1078)
      - 18-646 - 18-652, 19-1 - 19-39 (Box 1079)
      - 19-40 - 19-75 (Box 1080)
      - 19-76 - 19-125 (Box 1081)
      - 19-126 - 19-159 (Box 1082)
      - 19-160 - 19-200 (Box 1083)
      - 19-201 - 19-255 (Box 1084)
      - 19-256 - 19-300 (Box 1085)
      - 19-301 - 19-327 (Box 1086)
      - 19-328 - 19-367 (Box 1087)
      - 19-368 - 19-385, 20-1 - 20-49 (Box 1088)
      - 20-50 - 20-106 (Box 1089)
      - 20-107 - 20-182 (Box 1090)
      - 20-183 - 20-250 (Box 1091)
      - 20-251 - 20-288, 21-1 - 21-50 (Box 1092)
      - 21-51 - 1-120 (Box 1093)
      - 21-121 - 21-129, 22-1 - 22-86 (Box 1094)
      - 22-87 - 22-189 (Box 1095)
      - 22-190 - 22-282, 23-1 - 23-15 (Box 1096)
      - 23-16 - 23-115 (Box 1097)
      - 23-116 - 23-250 (Box 1098)
      - 23-251 - 23-349 (Box 1099)
      - 23-350 - 23-444 (Box 1100)
      - 24-1 - 24-90 (Box 1101)
      - 24-91 - 24-180 (Box 1102)
      - 24-181 - 24-285 (Box 1103)
      - 24-286 - 24-399 (Box 1104)
      - 24-400 - 24-499 (Box 1105)
      - 24-500 - 24-620 (Box 1106)
      - 24-621 - 24-676, 25-1 - 25-25 (Box 1107)
      - 25-26 - 25-100 (Box 1108)
      - 25- 101 - 25-184 (Box 1109)
      - 25-185 - 25-259 (Box 1110)
      - 25-260 - 25-330 (Box 1111)
      - 25-331 - 25-420 (Box 1112)
      - 25-421 - 25-490 (Box 1113)
      - 25-491 - 25-555 (Box 1114)
      - 25-556 - 25-652 (Box 1115)
      - 26-1 - 26-104 (Box 1116)
      - 26-105 - 26-190 (Box 1117)
      - 26-191 - 26-290 (Box 1118)
      - 26-291 - 26-400 (Box 1119)
      - 26-401 - 26-461, 27-1 - 27-35 (Box 1120)
      - 27-36 - 27-147 (Box 1121)
      - 27-148 - 27-235 (Box 1122)
      - 27-236 - 27-333 (Box 1123)
      - 27-334 - 27-438 (Box 1124)
      - 27-439 - 27-500, 28-1 - 28-35 (Box 1125)
      - 28-36 - 28-131 (Box 1126)
      - 28-132 - 28-199 (Box 1127)
      - 28-200 - 28-290 (Box 1128)
      - 28-291 - 28-351 (Box 1129)
      - 28-352 - 28-397, 29-1 - 29-30 (Box 1130)